healthyaperture.com 2017-05-18

# A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

This privacy policy sets out how Healthy Aperture (owned and managed by
ReganMillerJones, Inc.) uses and protects any information that you give while using
HealthyAperture.com.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using
this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy
statement.
Healthy Aperture (owned and managed by ReganMillerJones, Inc.) may change this policy
from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to
ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from September 11,
2013 .
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
    •   contact information including email address
    •   demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
    •   other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
    •   We may use the information to improve our products and services.
    •   We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or
        other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address
        which you have provided.
    •   From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market
        research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to
        customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent
unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and
managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know
when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an
individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by
gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data
about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We
only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from
the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which
pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your
computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept
cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.
This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Advertising
Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over
cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present
advertisements on the website, one of which is http://www.gourmetads.com. These vendors
may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored
to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to
determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you
duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as
your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed,
ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar
technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not
ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.
Links to other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to
leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which
you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy
statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the
website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the use of your personal information by emailing
healthyaperture@gmail.com. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal
information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by
contacting us.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have
your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to
send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find
interesting.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please
contact us.
